<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patrick Weston</title>
    <link>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Patrick Weston</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 19:48:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.patrickfweston.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel as my therapy</title>
      <link>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/travel-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 19:48:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/travel-therapy/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a regular follower of my content on Instagram, you know that I have traveled quite a bit this year. I’ve headed to all corners of the US: Boston, Vermont and Montreal; Florida; Texas, Arizona and New Mexico; Yellowstone, Portland, Seattle and Vancouver. I absolutely love to travel and to see how other people live, but I wanted to clear up the reason of why I’ve traveled so much this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Race to 50 States</title>
      <link>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/race-fifty-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 17:29:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/race-fifty-states/</guid>
      <description>.video-gif { img { display: block; } video { display: none; } @media only screen and (min-width: 768px) { img { display: none; } video { display: block; } } }  Growing up, roadtrips were a common occurrence. Now, I know what you&amp;rsquo;re picturing: the whole family hopping in the car during the summer and making the drive to Florida. We absolutely did that. But we also traveled throughout the year across the Midwest and the rest of the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worth my weight</title>
      <link>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/worth-my-weight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 09:14:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/worth-my-weight/</guid>
      <description>According to my mom, I was a big baby when I was born. I clocked in at about 9 pounds…and I was 4 weeks early. From birth to about age 15 I was definitely on the bigger side. I was never too overweight, but let’s just say that when I went back to school shopping for a new pair of jeans they had to be a husky fit.
Because of my larger than normal size, I grew to be very self conscious of my weight and self-appearance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traveling with Yourself</title>
      <link>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/traveling-with-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 20:29:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/traveling-with-yourself/</guid>
      <description>This week, I took a trip to Boston for work. Flight prices were cheaper to return on Sunday rather than Friday or Saturday, so I decided to make a trip out out of it. I also have a life goal of visiting all 50 U.S. States, and I was missing Vermont. I figured if I were that close I should take advantage of the opportunity.

Boston I was in Boston from Wednesday through Friday, and I caught the string of extremely warm February weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Bake Sale</title>
      <link>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/virtual-bake-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 21:49:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/virtual-bake-sale/</guid>
      <description>My coworker is helping to sponsor a refugee family of 9 through an organization called No One Left Behind.
 No One Left Behind supports wartime allies (interpreters, soldiers, cultural advisors, and other allies of American troops) who have been displaced from their home due to their association and support to Americans.
 The family has been in Chicago for a year. The father supports the family of 9 on one salary, but he has been unemployed for the last two months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are All Humans</title>
      <link>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/we-are-all-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 20:11:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.patrickfweston.com/post/we-are-all-humans/</guid>
      <description>Anyone who knows me fairly well knows that I&amp;rsquo;m Catholic. To some though, the subject may never come up or we never get a chance to know each other close enough for it to be revealed. I keep things pretty under wraps publicly&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid to share my faith, but I want to do it in a way that is organic. St. Francis of Assisi sums up my philosophy best:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>